Gene Grove

Chicago, IL 60608 gwg1387@gmail.com (574)-361-6003

Business Analyst with over 5 years of experience testing, monitoring, and implementing enterprise solutions for Fortune 500 companies, government agencies, and small enterprises. Ensured data consistency across 28 departments for budgets in excess of \$2 million per department. Core competencies include data management and aggregation, software development, customer relationship management, process improvement, quality assurance testing, budget management, event coordination, regulatory compliance, technical writing, and team management.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Food Expeditor

Tao Chicago June 2019 to Present

- Responsible for checking the quality and consistency of products before providing them to the customers.
- Monitoring inventory levels in order to provide accurate lead times for management.
- Trained and provided management with feedback on the fit of newly onboarded team members.

Logistical Coordinator

Blank Box LLC

October 2017 to Present

- Contacted venues on behalf of artists and maintaining relationships with venues.
- Scheduling events; seeking out venues, booking available artists, and working alongside the marketing
- Keeping ledgers up to date; collecting payment from venues and ensuring artists were paid on time and in full.

Server's Assistant

Tao Chicago

October 2018 to June 2019

- Providing support to the server and management teams throughout the course scheduled work.
- Worked with management to create a more cohesive work environment by enacting viable solutions to scheduling conflicts.

Consultant

CGI Federal on contract to the Nuclear Regulatory Commission - Lebanon, VA November 2013 to April 2017

- Tracked and tested solutions for customer software issues.
- Maintained customer budgets and tracked down the causes of any inconsistencies.

Business Analyst

CGI Federal

January 2013 to April 2017

- Monitored database logs isolating the root cause behind server failures.
- Tested new software patches with specific customer scenarios in mind.
- Maintained and updated documentation on 3 distinct software modules.

Server/Caterer

Hacienda Mexican Restaurant January 2008 to January 2013

- Managed catered events from start to finish; Verified contents of the order, set up and tore down requested events, billed and collected payments from customers
- Logged miles and maintained log information about the company van used in events.
- Provided guests with unique experiences satisfying their individualized needs.

Education

Bachelor's in Management of Information Systems and International BusinessIndiana University South Bend 2012

Skills

- Business Analysis
- Process Improvement
- Software Development
- · Software Testing